globalcollect.com 2008-10-19

# GlobalCollect Privacy Policy - committed to honoring the privacy of users and merchants

Privacy Policy 

At GlobalCollect we are committed to honoring the privacy of our users and merchant-partners. This privacy policy covers the processing of personally identifiable information shared through GlobalCollect´s services in accordance with the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act (the "Wet bescherming Persoonsgegevens").

What information does GlobalCollect receive and how do we use it?

When you use the GlobalCollect payments® some personal information is required. At a minimum, this would be your first and last name, address (country - if applicable), phone number, e-mail address and financial information such as your bank account number and /or credit card number. The level and volume of the required information is determined by the selected payment option. This information facilitates us to provide you with our payment services. In order to fulfil our roll as intermediary payment solution provider, GlobalCollect furthermore receives from her merchant-partner, with whom you placed an order, information on the products/services you bought. Furthermore GlobalCollect has to share the information provided by you with your bank/credit card company. In short GlobalCollect uses your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of rendering the GlobalCollect services. GlobalCollect shall not process these data any further and/or keep this data in any database longer than strictly necessary for these purposes. 

Security

It is GlobalCollect´s goal to provide its customers with a safe and secure shopping experience. A transaction by credit card with the GlobalCollect payments® service is in general even safer than payment by credit card via the e-mail or telephone. GlobalCollect´s secure server encrypts all your personal information (including name and address) so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the internet. When you enter this information it is captured on a page that uses the Secure Socked Layer (SSL) protocol by default. In order to be certain that you are connected to a real GlobalCollect payment® window, you can click on the little lock that appears at the bottom of the window as soon as the connection has been made secure. Then check whether you are connected to the GlobalCollect.com server. GlobalCollect makes use of a 128 bits Thawte certificate for the payments pages and we use 3Des encryption for the credit card authorization.

Cookies

Finally, like most websites, we store small pieces of information, called cookies on your computer´s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to gain information on the use of our services. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website you can contact: [info@GlobalCollect.com](mailto:info@GlobalCollect.com). 

Disclaimer

****GlobalCollect Payments® does not guarantee that the goods or services ordered will be delivered in accordance with the specifications or agreements. GlobalCollect guarantees only that the payment via GlobalCollect Payments® will be handled in a correct and reliable manner. GlobalCollect is not liable for all personal data stored in any data-base at our merchant-partners or any third parties which GlobalCollect uses to process the payments.
